Let's talk about the task board,
often called a Kanban board.
So Assad has been talking about agile a
lot throughout the class.
So you already know communications are
transparent.
They have on the board information
radiator, all project information,
burn up charts, burn down charts,
velocity charts.
Kanban or task boards.
They are very transparent in communications,
which I think is a very good thing.
So on this information radiator,
remember it's a large area near the team
who's supposed to be co-located if it's
all possible.
All that information is there.
So there is transparency.
All right.
So the task board can show the different
stories.
These are the to-do.
And so they look like a little post-its.
And a lot of times they use post-it notes.
So what stories still need to be done?
What's the work in progress?
What still has to be tested, verified and
what is done so that the team and any
stakeholder who comes by can see exactly
the progress of the project.
It's a great idea.
So I think we should do more of those no
matter what type of project you have.